<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Hulk's Blog | Frontend | Javascript</title><link>https://blog.bighulk.net/</link><description>LoveIt</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 11:14:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.bighulk.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Corn: Unix-like Scheduing</title><link>https://blog.bighulk.net/2023/03/16/20230315_cron/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 11:14:11 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://blog.bighulk.net/2023/03/16/20230315_cron/</guid><description>Introduction Cron is a time-based job scheduler in Unix-like operating systems. It allows users to execute commands automatically at specified intervals or times. Cron is a powerful tool that can be used for a variety of tasks, from running backups to executing scripts, and its flexibility makes it a popular choice for system administrators and developers alike.
Basic Concept Cron is a daemon that runs in the background and checks the /etc/crontab file and the /etc/cron.</description></item><item><title>Hulk's NPM Choices: corn-parser</title><link>https://blog.bighulk.net/2023/03/16/20230315_npm_parser/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 10:45:48 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://blog.bighulk.net/2023/03/16/20230315_npm_parser/</guid><description>Hulk&amp;rsquo;s npm choices: corn-parser Chapter 1: Basic Information Corn-parser is an npm package that parses cron syntax, including timezones. It is available for use as an npm package and the source code can be found on Github at https://github.com/harrisiirak/cron-parser. The package can be installed using npm with the command npm install cron-parser.
Corn-parser has over 2 million weekly downloads and has over 30 dependent packages. The three most famous dependent packages are:</description></item><item><title>Hulk NPM Choices: Validator</title><link>https://blog.bighulk.net/2023/03/14/20230314_npm_validator/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 15:28:20 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://blog.bighulk.net/2023/03/14/20230314_npm_validator/</guid><description>Hulk NPM Choices: Validator Introduction Data validation and sanitization are crucial aspects of any web application. In the world of JavaScript, the validator package is one of the most popular tools for string validation and sanitization. It provides a wide range of methods that make it easy to validate and sanitize strings, ensuring that your application is secure and performs well. In this blog, we will cover everything you need to know about the validator package, from its basic information to best practices for using it in your applications.</description></item></channel></rss>